Guide to the School of Nursing, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1975-1986; Accession 1990-A-005
  - Medical-Surqical Nursing
    - Course Plan, 1983-1984 (Box 641, Folder 143)
    - Expansion of Medical/Surgical Adv-Training 1D23NU00265-02, 1982-1984 (Box 641, Folder 144)
    - N610 - Conceptual Basis of Nursing, 1983-1984 (Box 641, Folder 145)
    - N610 - Expanded Role, 1983-1984 (Box 641, Folder 146)
    - N612b - Clinical Nursing Management - Med-Surg, Pulmonary, Cardiovascular, Neurological Cancer, 1983-1984 (Box 641, Folder 147)
    - N515b - Common Clinical Management Problems, 1983-1984 (Box 641, Folder 148)
    - N810a - Clinical Management 11: Cancer, Cardiovascular Med-Surg., Neurological, Surgica, 1983-1984 (Box 641, Folder 149)
    - N811a - Seminar in Role Development, 1983-1984 (Box 641, Folder 150)
    - N812b - Practicum in Role Development: Cancer, Surgical, 1983-1984 (Box 641, Folder 151)
    - N813b - Dimensions of Health Care, 1983-1984 (Box 641, Folder 152)
    - N815 a/b - Specialty Seminar: Med-Surg.Shared Classes, Cancer, Cardiovascular, Neurological, Surgical, 1983-1984 (Box 641, Folder 153)
  - Pediatric Nursing Proqram
    - Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 641, Folder 154)
    - Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 641, Folder 156)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1979-80 (Box 641, Folder 157)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1980-81 (Box 641, Folder 158)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 641, Folder 159)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes - schedules, 1982-1983 (Box 641, Folder 160)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes - Course Schedule, 1982-1983 (Box 641, Folder 161)
    - Student Orientation Materials, 1983-1984 (Box 641, Folder 162)
    - Adv pediatric Practitioner C l h Training, NU000664, 1983-1984 (Box 641, Folder 163)
    - Course Summaries, 1982-1983 (Box 641, Folder 164)
    - Employer Questionnaires, 1982 (Box 641, Folder 165)
    - First Year Student Evaluations, 1981 (Box 641, Folder 166)
    - First Year Student Evaluations, 1982 (Box 641, Folder 167)
    - First Year Student Evaluations, 1983 (Box 641, Folder 168)
    - Second Year Student Evaluations, 1982 (Box 641, Folder 169)
    - Second Year Student Evaluations, 1983 (Box 641, Folder 170)
    - N518 - Clinical Practice in Pediatric Nursing. Syllabus, 1982-1983 (Box 642, Folder 171)
    - N519 - Seminar in Pediatric Nursing, Syllabus, 1982-1984 (Box 642, Folder 172)
    - N530 - Health Assessment, Syllabus, 1981-1983 (Box 642, Folder 173)
    - N632 - Pediatric Primary Care Syllabus, 1981-1983 (Box 642, Folder 174)
    - N633 - Well Child Case, Syllabus, 1982-1983 (Box 642, Folder 175)
    - N634 - Perinatal Clinical Practice, Syllabus, 1981-1984 (Box 642, Folder 176)
    - N635 - Mgt.of Common Pediatric Problems, Syllabus, 1981-1984 (Box 642, Folder 177)
    - M637 - Child Development 11, Syllabus, 1981-1984 (Box 642, Folder 178)
    - N639 - Perinatal Clinical Management, Syllabus and Handouts, 1982-1983 (Box 642, Folder 179)
    - N640 - Clinical Practice in Primary Care of Adolescents, 1981-1984 (Box 642, Folder 180)
    - N641 - Caretaking Process in Adolescence Syllabus 1982-1984 (Box 643, Folder 181)
    - N831 - PNP Seminar, Syllabus, 1981-1984 (Box 643, Folder 182)
    - N639 - Perinatal Clinical Mgt, Syllabus and Handouts, Fall (see folder 179), 0 (Box 643, Folder 182a)
    - N830 - Primary Care of Children 11, Syllabus, 1981-1984 (Box 643, Folder 183)
    - N833 - Adv-Management - Syllabus and Handouts, 1981-1984 (Box 643, Folder 184)
    - N837 - Handicapped and Chronically 111 Child, Syllabus,Kandouts, 1982-1983 (Box 643, Folder 185)
    - N839 - Adv.Adolescent Seminar I, Syllabus, 1981-1983 (Box 643, Folder 186)
    - N840 - Adv.Practice in Adolescent Health Care, Syllabus, 1982-1983 (Box 643, Folder 187)
  - Psychiatric-Mental Health Nursing Proqram
    - PMHNP portion of Med.Surg.grant application: Maint/strengthening Clin.Pr.Acute Care. Approved, not funded, 1982 (Box 643, Folder 188)
    - PMHNP Course Schedule, 1984-85 (Box 643, Folder 189)
    - PMHNP Descriptive Brochure, 1984 (Box 643, Folder 190)
    - PMHNP Parttime Curriculum, 1984 (Box 643, Folder 191)
    - PMHNP Program-based appointments committee, 1984-85 (Box 643, Folder 192)
    - PMHNP N520b: Clin. Pract. PMH Nsg. Basic Rotation, S. Talley, 1984 (Box 643, Folder 193)
    - PMHNP N521b: Sem.in Clincal Nursing, PMH Basic Rotation, S.Talley, 1984 (Box 643, Folder 194)
    - PMHNP N650a: Basic Group Dynamics, N. Lifton, 1984-85 (Box 643, Folder 195)
    - PMKNP N656: Clin.Practice, PMK Nsg., 1984-85 (Box 643, Folder 196)
    - PMHNP Patient Contact Sheets, Semester I, Sept-Dec., 1984 (Box 643, Folder 197)
    - PMHNP Patient Contact Sheets, Semester 11, January-May, 1984 (Box 643, Folder 198)
    - Chronic Care, Adv.Psych.Nursing (D.Banchik), 1979-1984 (Box 643, Folder 199)
    - PMHNP N657a: Psych. Assessment and Therapy D.Davis/H.Vartelas, 1984 (Box 643, Folder 200)
    - PMHNP N65 7a: Individual Asessment and therapy (workbook), 1984 (Box 644, Folder 201)
    - PMHNP N659a/b: Psychopathology/Human Behavior. M-Visintainer, 1983-1984 (Box 644, Folder 202)
    - PMHNG65 9a: Psychopathol/Human Behavior, M.Visintainer/lst yr, 1984 (Box 644, Folder 203)
    - PMHNP N661a: Health Care Issues i n PMH. S. Talley, 1984 (Box 644, Folder 204)
    - PMNHP N663b: Group Psychotherapy Sem., L-Swearingen, January, 1984 (Box 644, Folder 205)
    - PMNRP N670a/b: Child Psychiatric Nsg. Practice, Pearson/Rooney, 1984-1985 (Box 644, Folder 206)
    - N854: Adv. Clin. Practicum in Nsg.of Chronically Ill Psych. Pts., 1984 (Box 644, Folder 207)
    - PMfINP N858a/b: Group Psychotherapy Clin.Pract., L. Swearingen, 1984 (Box 644, Folder 208)
    - PWNP N859: Group Psychotherapy Seminar, LSwearingen, 1984 (Box 644, Folder 209)
    - PMHNP N861a: Psych. Clin. Nse Spec. Indirect Care Role, D.Davis, 1984 (Box 644, Folder 210)
    - PMHNP N866: Adv. Clin. fracticum in Child Psych.Nsg, G-Pearson, 1984 (Box 644, Folder 211)
    - PMKNP N867a/b: Adv.Child Psych. Nsg. Seminar, Pearson/Rooney, 1984-1985 (Box 644, Folder 212)
  - Research proqram
    - Relaxation Therapy on Post-MI Patients, NU01052-01 B.Munro), 1983-1986 (Box 644, Folder 213)
    - N525b: Statistics (course materials and exams), 1983 (Box 644, Folder 214)
    - N715a: Computer Analysis of Data [course materials and exams), 1983 (Box 644, Folder 215)
    - N525a: Statistics (course materials), 1983 (Box 644, Folder 216)
    - N525b: Statistics (course materials and exams), 1984 (Box 644, Folder 217)
    - N527b: Clinical Research Seminar (course materials), 1984 (Box 644, Folder 218)
    - N715b: Computer Analysis of Data (course materials and exams), 1984 (Box 644, Folder 219)
    - Memos, Minutes, Annual Report, Announcements, 1983-1984 (Box 644, Folder 220)
    - Research Program - Annual Reports, 1976-79, 1982-1983 (Box 644, Folder 221)
- Records concerning the decision to cut the Master's program, 1918-1975; Accession 1992-A-042
  - Papers on the Yale School of Nursing, 1918-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Clippings, 1946-1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Printed materials, 1922-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Committee minutes and self-study report, 1990-1991; Accession 2009-A-148; 0.25; (1 box)
  Restricted until January 1, 2026
  - Committee minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Self-study report, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - YSN Report Correspondence, computer files, 3 (Reel 3)
      Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
- Commencement records, 2006-2010; Accession 2010-A-099
  The materials are open for research.
  - Comencement programs and cards, 2006-2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Commencement ceremony, speech, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Commencement ceremony, general, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Records of Donna Diers, Yale School of Nursing, 1957-1996; Accession 2013-A-068
  Restricted until January 1, 2031
  - Curriculum change report, 1957, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Diers personnel file, 1967-1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Nursing research program reports, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Faculty research development grants-follow up reports, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Faculty research development grant-response to proposal, Circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Research development projects-meeting transcripts, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annual report, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Nurse practitioner training-YSN compliance to federal grant regulations, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
  - Nurse practitioner training-YSN compliance to federal grant regulations, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Primary Care Center-use of nurse practitioners, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Response to union organizing, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - RIMS/nurse acuity project, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Records, 1989-2013; Accession 2014-A-001
  - Annual reports
    - 2007-2008
      - Documentation, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
      - Proofs and documentation, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
      - Final, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    - 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
    - 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
  - Associations
    - American Academy of Nursing (AAN)-Alexander and Sadler, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - American Academy of Nursing/Council for the Advancement of Science (AAN/CANS), 2011 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - American Association of Colleges of Nursing (AACN)
      - Annual Survey
        - 2007 (Box 1, Folder 14)
        - 2008 (Box 1, Folder 15)
        - 2009 (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
          General
          Includes faculty-doctoral students roster
        - 2010 (Box 1, Folder 18)
        - 2011 (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
          Includes faculty and doctoral student survey
      - Comission on Collegiate Nursing Education standards and procedures, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - American Diabetes Association Editorial Board acceptance form, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - American Nurses Credentialing Center, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Center for Healthcare Insurance, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Connecticut/National Council Licensure Examination (NCLEX) RN candidates, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Friends of the National Institute of Nursing Research (FNINR) 25th anniversary, 2010 September 29 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - National Council Licensure Examination (NCLEX) pass rates, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - National League for Nursing annual survey
      - 2008 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - 2009 (Box 1, Folder 30-31)
        Includes fall survey and faculty roster
      - 2010 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Nightingala
      - 2007 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - 2008 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Chronological files
    - 2007 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 2008 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 2009 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Commencement
    - 2005 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - 2007 (Box 2, Folder 38A)
    - 2008 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - 2009 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - 2010 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - 2011 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Committees
    - Center of Excellence Task Force, 2002-2007 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Comittees, 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Committee selection-Yale School of Nursing, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Doctoral program, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Doctor of Nursing Practice (DNP) Task Force, 2008 October 8 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Doctor of Nursing Practice Program Committee report, 2008 October 8 (Box 2, Folder 47a)
    - DSMB for "Adolscents with Type 1 Diabetes", 2011 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Exam Construction Task Force retreat, 2008 October 10 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Executive Committee-Yale School of Nursing, Voted Documents, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - External Advisory Board-Yale School of Nursing, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Midwifery (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Net Haven Practice Based Research Network Advisory Board, 2011 March 3 (Box 2, Folder 53A)
    - "Optimizing Self-Management Adherence and Glycemic Control in Older Teens with T1D"-Data and Safety Monitoring Committee correspondence, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - P30 External Advisory Committee, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Part-time lecture database, 2008-2010 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Self-management executive committee, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Strategic Advisory Committee (Provost's Office), 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - YSN Standing Committees selection process, 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 58A)
  - Faculty
    - Retreat, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - New faculty orientation, 2008 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Handbook revisions, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Faculty merit review, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Annual review, 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Government
    - Connecticut
      - AIDS Education and Training Center, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 73)
      - Board of Examiners, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 73a)
      - Board of Nurse Examiners-meeting agenda, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 74)
      - Department of Education, 1990-2002 (Box 3, Folder 75)
      - Department of Health, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 76)
      - Connecticut Fund for the Environment, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 77)
      - Regulations of nursing education, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Federal
      - Federal regulations, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 81)
      - Legislation-federal (Box 3, Folder 82)
      - Richard Jacobs and federal regulations, 1998-2003 (Box 3, Folder 83)
      - Senate hearing on obsesity-Margaret Grey testimony, 2008 July 16 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - International affairs
    - Sungshin Women's University/Whitney Center/Yale School of Nursing collaboration, 1995-2009 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Peking University People's Hospital, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Ramathibodi Hospital Bangkok, Thailand-partnership program memorandum of agreement, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Royal University of Bhutan, 2011-2012 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Shanghai Lida Polytechnic Institute, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Srinakharinwirot University School of Nursing visit, 2011 May 17-18 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - University of Hong Kong
      - 2008 (Box 3, Folder 91)
      - 2009 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Hong Kong Polytechnic University, 2010-2013 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Mahidol University faculty, 2009 March 9-10 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Oxford Brookes University, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Partnership program agreement with Chulalongkorn University, Thailand, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Kang Hyun Sook-Kongju National University Department of Nursing, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - China-memorandum of agreement and abstract, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - China Fellows, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 99A)
    - China-Central South University School of Nursing study tour, 2011 July 25-27 (Box 3, Folder 99B)
    - Chiba University School of Nursing, Japan, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 99C)
  - Yale School of Nursing files
    - Events
      - Associate Dean's retreat, 2008 June 2 (Box 3, Folder 100)
      - Bellos Lecture
        - 2002 (Box 3, Folder 101)
          File includes photographs
        - 2007 (Box 3, Folder 102)
        - 2008 (Box 3, Folder 103)
        - 2009 (Box 3, Folder 104)
        - 2010 (Box 3, Folder 105)
        - 2011 (Box 3, Folder 106)
      - Convocation, 2008 April 3 (Box 4, Folder 107)
      - Creative writing awards, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 108)
      - Donna Diers Living Legend Award ceremony/reception, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 109)
      - Rheutaugh Dumas tribute, 2008 February 5 (Box 4, Folder 110)
      - Elm-Ivy Award
        - 2000 (Box 4, Folder 111)
        - 2002 (Box 4, Folder 112)
        - 2003 (Box 4, Folder 113)
        - 2007 (Box 4, Folder 114)
      - Employee Recognition
        - 2007 (Box 4, Folder 115)
        - 2008 (Box 4, Folder 116)
      - Fair Haven Community Health Center-40th anniversary, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 117)
      - Graduate Entry Program in Nursing (GEPN) Certification ceremony
        - 2007 (Box 4, Folder 118)
        - 2008 (Box 4, Folder 119)
        - 2009 (Box 4, Folder 120)
      - Health Camp, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 121)
      - Hill Health Center-40th anniversary, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 122)
      - Kennedy, Holly reception, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 123)
      - Nightingale Awards
        - 2007 (Box 4, Folder 124)
        - 2008 April (Box 4, Folder 125)
        - 2008 May (Box 4, Folder 126)
        - 2010 May 5 (Box 4, Folder 127)
        - 2011 April 13 (Box 4, Folder 127A)
        - 2011 May 5 (Box 4, Folder 128)
      - Orientation speech, 2007 August 27 (Box 4, Folder 129)
      - Reunion weekend, 2004 June 3-5 (Box 4, Folder 130)
      - Rousseau, Mary Ellen reception at American College of Nurse Midwives conference, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 131)
      - Sigma Theta Tau induction ceremony
        - 2009 (Box 4, Folder 132)
        - 2011 (Box 4, Folder 132a)
      - VA Center for Excellence Program site visit, 2012 March 20 (Box 4, Folder 133)
      - Yale School of Nursing Walk
        - 2010 (Box 4, Folder 134)
        - 2011 (Box 4, Folder 135)
      - Youth of the Hill reception, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Organizational files
      - Admissions, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 142)
      - Center for International Nursing Scholarship and Education-International Nursing Collaboration, 2008 February 1 (Box 4, Folder 144)
      - Connecticut Community College/YSN nursing program, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 145)
      - Conflict of interest policy, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 146)
      - Correspondence, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 147)
      - Clinical and Translational Science Award (CTSA) program visit, 2011 November 3-4 (Box 4, Folder 148)
      - Cushing-Whitney Memorial Library, Library Associates, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 149)
      - Doctor of Nursing Science (DNSc) program proposals, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 150)
      - Doctor of Nursing Science (DNSc) statistics, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 151)
      - Ethics conference, 2008 July 18 (Box 4, Folder 152)
      - Goals and Priorities
        - 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 153)
        - 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 154)
      - Graduate Entry Program in Nursing (GEPN)-faculty orientation and statistics, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 155)
      - Interim report, 2002 April (Box 4, Folder 157)
      - Master's program self-studies report and appendices, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 158)
      - New merit process notes, 2008 September (Box 4, Folder 159)
      - New Haven Free Clinic, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 160)
      - Nurse Midwifery speciality business plan, 2002-2009 (Box 4, Folder 161)
      - Nurse Practitioner scope of practice-Connecticut, 1998, Undated (Box 4, Folder 162)
      - Nurse researcher position-YNNH, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 163)
      - Office of Clinical and Community Affairs, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 164)
      - Photograph-Margaret Grey, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 165)
      - Research space assignments (Box 4, Folder 167)
      - Revision to Nursing regulations, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 168)
      - Space profile, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 169)
      - Space profile-originals, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 170)
      - State of the School Address
        - 2008 (Box 4, Folder 171)
        - 2009-2010 (Box 4, Folder 172)
      - Strategic Plan-Provost ad hoc committee, 1997-2002 (Box 4, Folder 173)
      - U.S. News and World Report: Best Online Nursing Degree, 2011-2012 (Box 4, Folder 174)
      - Varney Chair search committee, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - Yale University
    - Agreements and Negotiations-Yale/New Haven Medical Center, Undated (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - Collaborative practice meeting, 2007 June 5 (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - Information from President Levin, 2004-2010 (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Status of Minority Students in the Graduate and Professional Schools Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 178a)
    - University Budget Committee, 2006-2009 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - University Tribunal Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - Yale Center for Clinical Investigation, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 181-182)
    - Yale-China, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - Yale-Environmental Health and Safety (bloodborne pathogens), 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - Yale Global Health Initiative-Final Report, 2009-2012 (Box 6, Folder 185)
    - Yale-Howard Partnership Center, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 186)
    - Yale Medal, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 187)
    - Yale-New Haven Hospital-American Nurses Credentialing Center (ANCC) site visit, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 188)
    - Yale-New Haven Hospital Birth Center, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 189)
    - Yale School of Medicine Committee on Clinical Investigation report, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 189a)
    - Yale University Office of Equal Opportunity-Affirmative Action and Equal Opportunity Policies and University Grievance Procedures, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 190)
    - Yale University Title IX Sexual Harassment Procedures, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 191)
    - Yale Women Faculty Forum-child care research, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 192)
- Records, 1983-2008; Accession 2014-A-023
  - General
    - YSN Executive Committee history, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Practice Plan Task Force report, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Review of Clinical Enterprise report, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Board of Permanent Officers, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - YSN Tercentennial Committee, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Faculty governance presentation, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Center for Excellence in Chronic Illness files
    - Annual reports
      - 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Awards-Caring Awards
      - Research, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Award development, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Awardees, 1999-2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Award criteria, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Invitation/program, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Nominations/citations
        - 2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
        - 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - 2003 (Box 1, Folder 17-17A)
        - 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-18A)
        - 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 19)
        - 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Budgets
      - 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - 2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Convocations
      - Inaugural Convocation, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Second Convocation, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Third Convocation, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Fifth Convocation, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Sixth Convocation, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Seventh Convocation, 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Grant notes and background, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Meetings
      - 1998 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - 1999 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - 2003 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - 2004 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Ortho bio-tech research, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Doctor of Nursing Studies
    - National League of Nursing (NLN) questionnaire, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - NLN survey, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Memorandum, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 40)